Finding Aid for School of Education (University of Michigan) Records, 1904-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean's Files
  - Cecil Miskel, 1980-1998; 1988-1993
    - Development-School of Education
      - Correspondence
        - 1991-1992 (Box 64)
        - 1992-1993 (Box 64)
        - 1993-1994 (Box 64)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 64)
      - Major Donor Dinner, 6/13/1994 (Box 64)
      - Major Gifts Reception, 6/22/1994 (Box 64)
      - Trips, 1990 (Box 64)
    - Dissertations
      - Dissertation Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 64)
      - Policy, 1988-1989 (Box 64)
    - Directed Teaching
      - 1983-1984, 1986-1987 (Box 64)
      - Payroll, 1985-1986; 1987-1988 (Box 64)
    - Diversity Committee-School of Education
      - 1989-1990 (Box 64)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 64)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 64)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 64)
    - Division for Research Development and Administration
      - 1988-1989 (Box 64)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 64)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 64)
    - Dow Chemical Company, 5/6/1992 (Box 64)
    - Early Childhood Education, 1987-1988 (Box 64)
    - Eastern Michigan University Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 64)
    - Education Administration
      - 1/25/1993 (Box 64)
      - Planning, 1993-1994 (Box 64)
      - Reform, 1989-1990 (Box 64)
    - Education and the Economy, 1990-1993 (Box 64)
    - Education Indicators
      - Inputs, Processes, and Outputs, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Inputs and Processes, 9/30/1990 (Box 64)
      - Outputs and Outcomes, 9/30/1990 (Box 64)
      - Patterns of Resource Use
        - 9/30/1990 (Box 64)
        - General, Undated (Box 64)
    - Educational Administration Quarterly, 1989-1990 (Box 65)
    - Educational Extension Service, 1988-1989 (Box 65)
    - Educational Law Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 65)
    - Educational Leadership Program, 1988-1989 (Box 65)
    - Educational Research and Improvement, Office of (OERI)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 65)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 65)
      - Center Proposals
        - Undated (Box 65)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 65)
        - Cohen, 5/10/1995 (Box 65)
        - Maehr, 1990 (Box 65)
    - Educational Research Information Center (ERIC)
      - Counseling and Personnel Services (CAPS)
        - 1988-1989 (Box 65)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 65)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 65)
      - Memorandums, 1970s (Box 65)
    - Educational Studies Program
      - 1989-1990 (Box 65)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 65)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 65)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 65)
      - Faculty Letters, 1990-1991 (Box 65)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 65)
      - Orientation Lunch, 9/8/1993 (Box 65)
      - Time Schedule Fall, 1991 (Box 65)
    - Educational Technology, 1987-1988 (Box 65)
      [ER RESTRICTED until November 1, 2035
    - Educators Conference, 5/20/1994 (Box 65)
    - EDUCOM, 1989-1990 (Box 65)
    - EDUCOM/NCRIPTAL, 1989-1990 (Box 65)
    - Educational Foundations, Policy, and Administration (EFPA)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 65)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 65)
      - Annual Report
        - 1986-1987 (Box 65)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 65)
    - Engineering, College of, 1989-1990 (Box 65)
    - Enrollment
      - 1988-1989 (Box 65)
      - 1989 (Box 65)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 65)
      - Winter, 1991 (Box 65)
      - 1991 (Box 65)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 66)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 66)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 66)
      - LSB, 1991-1992 (Box 66)
      - Meeting
        - 11/23/1992 (Box 66)
        - 1/10/1994 (Box 66)
        - 11/21/1994 (Box 66)
      - Minority Enrollment in Teacher Preparation Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 66)
      - Tuition Revenue, 6/7/1995 (Box 66)
    - Ethics and Values, 1988-1989; 1990-1991 (Box 66)
    - Extension, Winter, 1995 (Box 66)
    - Faculty
      - Assignments, 1988-1989 (Box 66)
      - Awards, 1990-1991 (Box 66)
      - Congratulations, 1989-1990; 1990-1991 (Box 66)
      - Development Fund, 1988-1989 (Box 66)
      - Emeritus Club Induction Ceremony, 6/5/1993 (Box 66)
      - Endowed Professorships, 1984-1985 (Box 66)
      - Evaluation (1989-1990) (Box 81)
      - Faculty and Staff Meetings and Faculty Forum Meetings, 1989-1990; 1990-1991 (Box 66)
      - Forum
        - Undated (Box 66)
        - 10/12/1989 (Box 66)
      - "General" Faculty Position Opening, 1986-1988 (Box 66)
      - Meeting Minutes
        - 1980-1984 (Box 66)
        - 1987-1988 (Box 66)
        - 1988, 4 folders (Box 66)
        - 1989, 3 folders (Box 66)
        - 1990, 4 folders (Box 66)
        - 1991, 3 folders (Box 66)
        - 1992, 6 folders (Box 66)
        - 1993, 6 folders (Box 66)
        - 1994, 4 folders (Box 67)
        - 1995, 5 folders (Box 67)
        - 1996, 4 folders (Box 67)
        - 1997, 4 folders (Box 67)
        - 1998, 6 folders (Box 67)
        - 1999, 5 folders (Box 67)
        - Agendas, 1990s (Box 67)
        - Miscellaneous Materials, 1980-1985 (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous
        - 1990-1991 (Box 67)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 67)
      - Nettles, Michael T., 1988-1989 (Box 67)
      - New Faculty Members, 1989-1990 (Box 67)
      - Peterson, Marvin, 3/31/1994 (Box 67)
      - Planning Lunch
        - 6/4/1993 (Box 67)
        - 6/7/1993 (Box 67)
        - 6/14/1993 (Box 67)
      - Position Announcement, 1989-1990 (Box 67)
      - Promotion Committee (Box 81)
        - 1986-1987 (Box 81)
        - 1988-1989 (Box 81)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 81)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 81)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 81)
      - Promotion Policies and Procedures (1990-1991) (Box 68)
      - Requests for Sabbatical Leave
        - 12/1992 (Box 68)
        - 1993 (Box 68)
        - 12/1994 (Box 68)
        - 1995-1996 (Box 68)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 68)
        - 1997-1998 (Box 68)
      - Recruitment, 1988-1989; 1989-1990 (Box 68)
      - Searches
        - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 68)
        - Director of Teacher Education, 1995-1997 (Box 68)
        - Teacher Education Accreditation Council (TEAC), 1997-1998 (Box 68)
      - SEB Collegiate and Endowed Faculty Positions, 1994 (Box 68)
      - Senior Women Faculty Program, 1991-1992 (Box 68)
      - Tenure, 1989 (Box 68)
      - Untenured Assistant Professor One Year Review, 7/1992 (Box 68)
        [PR RESTRICTED until November 1, 2045
    - Field Placement, 1989-1990 (Box 68)
    - Financial Aid and Fellowships
      - 1987-1988 (Box 68)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 68)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 68)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 68)
      - Tuition Assistantship Fellow, 12/9/1993 (Box 68)
    - Financial Operations, 1989-1990 (Box 68)
    - Flint, University of Michigan
      - Campus, 1984-1986 (Box 68)
      - Department of Education Minutes, 1988-1989; 1989-1990 (Box 68)
    - Fresh Air Camp, 1988-1989 (Box 68)
    - Fulbright Research Scholar Program, 1989-1990 (Box 68)
      [PR PRRESTRICTED until November 1, 2045
    - Future Educators, 1987-1988 (Box 68)
    - Future Problem Solving Program FDSD, 1988-1989 (Box 68)
    - Graduate Affair Committee (GAC)
      - 3/4/1993 (Box 68)
      - 4/1/1993 (Box 68)
      - Agenda Items and Meeting Minutes (1985-1992), 51 folders (Box 81)
        [SR RESTRICTED until November 1, 2090 ]
      - Best Dissertation Awards (Box 68)
        - 1982 (Box 68)
        - 1985 (Box 68)
        - 1986 (Box 68)
        - 1987 (Box 68)
        - 1988, 2 folders (Box 68)
        - 1989 (Box 68)
      - Chairing Dissertation Committee, 1980s (Box 68)
      - Charge, 1989 (Box 68)
      - Cognate Requirements, 1989 (Box 68)
      - Core Courses, 1987; 3 folders (Box 68)
      - Correspondence
        - 1990-1991 (Box 68)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 68)
      - Curriculum Changes, 1989 (Box 68)
      - Degree Programs, 1986 (Box 68)
      - Dissertation Designate, 1985-1986 (Box 69)
      - Dissertation Grant Committee, 1988 (Box 69)
      - Dissertation Quality Discussion, 1990-1991 (Box 69)
      - Distinction between Ed.D & Ph.D, 1986-1987 (Box 69)
      - Education 695 Equivalent Criteria, 1988 (Box 69)
      - Education Studies Guidelines, 1986 (Box 69)
      - Faculty Dissertation Chair Review, 1987 (Box 69)
      - Financial Aid, 1990-1991 (Box 69)
      - Grading Policies, Undated (Box 69)
      - GRE Exam, 1990 (Box 69)
      - Human Subjects Review Board Issues, 1993 (Box 69)
      - Individualized Interdepartmental Degree Program (IIDP), 1988 (Box 69)
      - Implementation of Report on Improving Dissertation Quality, 1990s; 4 folders (Box 69)
      - Jan Lawrence, 1990-1991 (Box 69)
      - Log of Dissertation CHS/COMMS, 1989 (Box 69)
      - Log of Petitions
        - 1985-1986 (Box 69)
        - 1986-1987 (Box 69)
      - Membership, 1991-1992 (Box 69)
      - Merit Awards, 1990 (Box 69)
      - Minority Fellowships, 1989 (Box 69)
      - Mult. Manuscript Dissertations, 1987 (Box 69)
      - One Term Dissertation Fellowship, 1990s (Box 69)
      - Packet of Info for New Members, 1987 (Box 69)
      - PhD. Reinstatement, 1990 (Box 69)
      - Petitions (1985-1986)(2 Folders) (Box 81)
      - Predoctoral Fellowships (1993), 4 folders (Box 81)
      - Rackham, 1991-1992 (Box 69)
      - Rackham Block Grant (1990) (Box 81)
      - Rackham Predoctoral Fellowship, 1990 (Box 69)
      - Rackham Thesis/Dissertation Grants, 1989 (Box 69)
      - Rackham/School of Education Admissions Agreement, 1980s (Box 69)
      - Regents Fellowship, 1990 (Box 69)
      - Student Quality Index, 1987 (Box 69)
      - Subcommittee on Dissertations, 1987 (Box 69)
    - Graduate Curriculum Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 69)
    - Graduate Student Organization, 1988-1989 (Box 69)
    - Grievance Proceedings: Nancy Bromberg (Box 81)
    - GSA, GSTA, ect Correspondence, 1988-1989; 1989-1990 (Box 69)
    - Higher and Adult Continuing Education (HACE)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 69)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 69)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 69)
      - Budget Meeting, 1991 (Box 69)
      - Meeting with Marvin Peterson, 8/16/1991 (Box 69)
    - High School Futures Planning Conference, 1989-1990 (Box 70)
    - Holmes Group
      - From Cecil, 1988-1989; 1990-1991 (Box 70)
      - Correspondence, 1988-1989; 1989-1990 (Box 70)
      - Executive Committee, 1988-1989; 1990-1991 (Box 70)
      - "Tomorrow's Schools", 1990-1991 (Box 70)
    - Hong Kong, 1990 (Box 70)
    - Human Subjects Review Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 70)
    - Human Resource Development, 1986-1991 (Box 70)
    - IBM
      - 1988-1989 (Box 70)
      - Academic Computing Conference
        - June 11-13, 1991 (Box 70)
        - JUne 8-11, 1992 (Box 70)
      - Center, 1989-1990 (Box 70)
      - Project-Blumenfeld, Soloway, 1988 (Box 70)
      - Proposal to the IBM Program for Teacher Preparation and Enhancement in the Use of Available Technology, 1989 (Box 70)
      - Seminar for Deans of Schools of Education-Austin, Texas, 6/11-6/13 (Box 70)
    - Ideas, 1988 (Box 70)
    - Individualized Interdepartmental Degree Program (IIDP), 1989 (Box 70)
    - Information and Library Studies, School of, 1989-1990 (Box 70)
    - Information Technology Division (ITD)
      - Events, 1995 (Box 70)
      - General, 1996 (Box 70)
      - School of Education Partnership, 1997 (Box 70)
      - World Wide Web, 1997 (Box 70)
    - Initiatives, 1986 (Box 70)
    - Innovator, 1994 (Box 70)
    - Instructional Technology, Office of
      - 1989-1990 (Box 70)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 70)
      - Program, 1991 (Box 70)
    - Intellectual Properties Office, 1993 (Box 70)
    - Interactive Communication Simulation, 1989-1992; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Institute for Research on Innovation and Science (IRIS)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 70)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 70)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 70)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 70)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 70)
    - Kellog Foundation Meeting, 1/11/1994 (Box 70)
    - King-Chavez-Parks Visiting Professor Program
      - 1990-1991
        - College Day Program, 1988-1991 (Box 70)
        - Michael Nettles, 1990-1991 (Box 70)
        - Michael Olivas, 1988-1989 (Box 70)
    - Western Kiwanis, Ann Arbor, 5/4/1993 (Box 70)
    - Land Grant Deans Association Clearwater, Florida, 10/26-10/30; 1990 (Box 70)
    - Lawrence, Jan
      - Correspondence to Jan Lawrence, 1991-1992 (Box 70)
      - Letters from Jan Lawrence (Box 70)
      - Memo
        - 1990-1991 (Box 70)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 70)
      - Personal, 1991-1992 (Box 70)
    - Literacy Education, 1994 (Box 71)
    - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of
      - 1988-1989 (Box 71)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 71)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 71)
    - M Campaign
      - 1992-1993 (Box 71)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 71)
      - Breakfast with the Dean, 9/27/1997 (Box 71)
      - Campaign Update, 12/22/1993 (Box 71)
      - Capital Campaign, 1991 (Box 71)
      - Celebration and Lunch, 9/26/1997 (Box 71)
      - Mid-Campaign/Alumni Gathering, 9/23-9/24; 1994 (Box 71)
      - Reception and Dinner, 9/26/1997 (Box 71)
      - School of Education, 1997 (Box 71)
    - Master of Arts with Certification (MAC)
      - Annual Recognition Ceremony, 7/31/1993 (Box 71)
      - Miscellaneous Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 71)
      - Program
        - 1991-1992, 2 folders (Box 71)
        - 1992-1993 (Box 71)
    - Management Council Meeting, 11/8/1990 (Box 71)
    - Martin Luther King Day Celebration
      - 1990-1991 (Box 71)
      - Symposium
        - 1988-1989 (Box 71)
        - 1990 (Box 71)
    - Martin Luther King/Rosa Parks Educational Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 71)
    - Marx Research Group, 6/1/1994 (Box 71)
    - Master's Degree
      - 1994-1995 (Box 71)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 71)
      - Sequences, 1987-1988 (Box 71)
      - Task Force, 1988 (Box 71)
    - Mathematics Education
      - 1993-1994 (Box 71)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 71)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 71)
    - Lunch with Meaders, 7/30/1993 (Box 71)
    - Meisels, Samuel Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 71)
    - Metropolitan Detroit Bureau of School Studies
      - General Information and Correspondence
        - Winter, 1988 (Box 71)
        - 1988 (Box 71)
        - Fall, 1989 (Box 71)
      - Presentation, 4/8/1991 (Box 72)
      - Meetings of the Board
        - 1988-1989 (Box 72)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 72)
      - Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 72)
      - Salary and Benefits of Administrative Staff, 1989-1990 (Box 72)
      - Salary Reports
        - 1988-1989 (Box 72)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 72)
    - Michigan Association of Colleges for Teacher Education (MACTE)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 72)
      - Executive Board Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 72)
      - General Correspondence
        - 1988-1989 (Box 72)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 72)
      - Newsletter
        - 1989-1990 (Box 72)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 72)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1988-1989 (Box 72)
    - Michigan Department of Education
      - Advisory Committee on Accreditation, 1989-1990 (Box 72)
      - Correspondence
        - 1989-1990 (Box 72)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 72)
    - Michigan Mandate, 1988-1991 (Box 72)
    - Michigan Partnership for New Education (MPNE) (Box 73)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 73)
      - Board of Directors Organizing Meeting, 1991 (Box 73)
      - Budget
        - Outline Draft
          - 11/20/1989 (Box 73)
          - 11/29/1989 (Box 73)
          - 12/1/1989 (Box 73)
          - 12/7/1989 (Box 73)
        - Professional Development Schools, Undated (Box 73)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1991 (Box 73)
      - Correspondence
        - 1989-1990 (Box 73)
        - 1989-1992 (Box 73)
        - 1992-1993 (Box 73)
        - 1993-1994 (Box 73)
      - Education Leadership Academies, 1990 (Box 73)
      - Educational Extension Service, 1991 (Box 73)
      - "House One", 1991 (Box 73)
      - Ingham Center for Education Leadership, 1990 (Box 73)
      - Joe & Stu, 11/21/1994 (Box 73)
      - Meeting
        - 5/16/1990 (Box 73)
        - 7/10/1990 (Box 73)
        - 8/31/1993 (Box 73)
      - Michigan Institute on Education and the Economy (MIEE), 1990 (Box 74)
      - Michigan Job Training Coordinating Council, 1990 (Box 74)
      - The Michigan Partnership for New Education: Situation Report for the Board of Directors, March 1991 (Box 74)
      - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 74)
      - Professional Development Schools (PDS)
        - Carpenter-Joseph Payne, 1991-1992 (Box 74)
        - Edmonson, 5/10/1995 (Box 74)
        - General, 1991 (Box 74)
        - General, 1995 (Box 74)
        - Jay Robinson, 1990 (Box 74)
        - Gary Knowles, 1990 (Box 74)
        - Willow Run Community Schools/Michigan Partnership, 1990 (Box 74)
      - Proposal Partnership, 1991 (Box 74)
      - Publicity, 1989-1990s (Box 74)
      - Site Visit Harrison Blackmond, 2/10/1993 (Box 74)
    - Michigan Reform Efforts Planning, 12/15/1993 (Box 74)
    - Michigan State University Faculty and University of Michigan Offers and Hirings, 1993 (Box 74)
    - Minority Affairs, Office of
      - 1988-1990 (Box 74)
      - Fireside Chat, 1988-1989 (Box 74)
      - Vice Provost Charles Moody
        - 1989-1989 (Box 74)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 74)
      - Student Services, 1989-1990 (Box 74)
      - Report, 1988-1989 (Box 74)
    - Minority Statistics, 1989-1990 (Box 74)
    - Multicultural University Retreat, 5/24/1994 (Box 74)
    - Multiculturalism, 1993-1994 (Box 74)
    - Murray Jackson Proposal, 1989 (Box 74)
    - National Center for Education Statistics-Reprint: Dropout Rates in the U.S., 1988 (Box 74)
    - National Commission on Excellence in Education--Utah's Response, 1983 (Box 74)
    - National Education Goals Panel, 1992-1993 (Box 74)
    - National Education Standards and Assessment Council, 1992-1993 (Box 74)
    - National Institute of Education in Singapore, 1994 (Box 74)
    - Natural Resources, School of, 1991-1992 (Box 74)
    - New American School Development Corporation, 1991-1992 (Box 74)
    - North Central Association of Colleges and Schools (NCAS)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 74)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 74)
    - Organizational Reports (1988-1989) (Box 74)
    - Partners for Excellence, 9/8/1994 (Box 74)
    - Partnerships, 1988 (Box 74)
    - Peace Corp (Box 75)
      - Background Information, 1991 (Box 75)
      - Correspondence
        - 1991 (Box 75)
        - 1992 (Box 75)
        - 1993 (Box 75)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 75)
      - Detroit Edison (1991-1992), 2 folders (Box 75)
      - Faculty Orientation Talks (8 Audiocassette Tapes) (Box 75)
      - Fellows/United States of America Agreements Budget, 1991 (Box 75)
      - Materials, 1992-1993 (Box 75)
      - Press, 1992 (Box 75)
      - Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 75)
    - Peterson, Mary Re: Nordby/Cook Appointments, 4/20/1992 (Box 75)
    - PhDs
      - Doctoral Degree in Education Studies Proposal by Ron Marx, 1992 (Box 75)
      - Doctoral Degree Planning Committee, 1994 (Box 75)
      - EdD/PhD Information, 1980s-1990s; 3 folders (Box 75)
      - New or Alternative Doctoral Program
        - Email, 1993 (Box 75)
        - Materials, 1994 (Box 75)
      - Proposal, 12/11/1992 (Box 75)
    - Policies, School of Education
      - Discrimination and Discriminatory Harassment by Students, 1988-1989 (Box 75)
      - Sexual Harassment Policy, 1990-1992 (Box 75)
      - Sexual Harassment Policy Revision, 1991-1992 (Box 75)
    - Power, Phillip, 1991-1992 (Box 75)
    - President, Office of
      - Duderstadt, 6/13/1994 (Box 75)
      - Presentation, 12/21/1993 (Box 75)
    - Presidential Initiative Fund, 1989-1991 (Box 75)
    - Procedures, 1991-1992 (Box 75)
    - Professional Development, 1988-1989 (Box 75)
    - Professional Teacher Corps., 1989 (Box 75)
    - Program Chairs, 1988-1989 (Box 76)
    - Program for Educational Opportunity, 1991 (Box 76)
    - Program in English and Education
      - 1988-1989 (Box 76)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 76)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 76)
      - 6/2/1993 (Box 76)
      - Jay Robinson, 1991-1992 (Box 76)
    - Project Steering Committee, Executive Liaison Committee, Tomorrow's Schools National Staff Meetings, 6/2-6/3, 1989 (Box 76)
    - Proposal A, 1989-1990 (Box 76)
    - Proposals
      - 1993-1994 (Box 76)
      - Annenberg Challenge Grant Information, 1997 (Box 76)
      - Center for a New American Education
        - Draft, 1989 (Box 76)
        - Proposal, 1989 (Box 76)
      - General, 1991 (Box 76)
      - Maehr, 1990 (Box 76)
      - Robert Kozma Project, 1991 (Box 76)
      - School Districts, 1990-1992 (Box 76)
      - Searle, 1991-1992 (Box 76)
      - Sloan Foundation Proposal, 1991 (Box 76)
      - Spencer Foundation Proposal
        - Colloquia, 1994 (Box 76)
        - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 76)
        - Email, 1993 (Box 76)
        - Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 76)
        - Original Proposal, 10/1993 (Box 76)
        - Preparation Materials, 10/1993 (Box 76)
        - Report, 1994-1995 (Box 77)
        - Site Visit
          - 10/27/1993 (Box 77)
          - 2/8/1995 (Box 77)
        - Supported by Cecil Miskel, 1991-1992 (Box 77)
      - United Auto-Workers-General Motors (UAW-GM) Proposal, 1989 (Box 77)
      - Urban Center Proposal-Detroit Rackham, Undated (Box 77)
    - Provost's Office
      - John Godfrey Request for Informal Working Document for NCA, 12/1998 (Box 77)
      - Meeting, 3/22/1991 (Box 77)
      - Provost Cantor, 1/22/1998 (Box 77)
      - Whitaker, 7/2/1991 (Box 77)
    - Psychology, Department of, 1990-1992 (Box 77)
    - Public Schools
      - Ann Arbor Public Schools
        - 1989-1990 (Box 77)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 77)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 77)
        - Initiatives, 1990 (Box 77)
      - Dearborn Public Schools, 1986-1987; 1987-1988 (Box 77)
      - Detroit Public Schools
        - 1988-1989 (Box 77)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 77)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 77)
        - 11/5/1993 (Box 77)
        - 6/6/1994 (Box 77)
      - Saginaw Public Schools, 1987-1988; 1988-1989 (Box 77)
      - School District Consolidation, 11/15/1993 (Box 77)
      - Superintendent Schiller, 3/3/1995 (Box 77)
      - Willow Run School District, 1991-1992 (Box 77)
    - Rackham
      - Basic Fellowships and Scholarships, 1991-1992 (Box 77)
      - General Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 77)
      - Letters to School of Education Faculty, 1990-1991 (Box 77)
      - Predoctoral Fellowship Selection Committee
        - 1989-1990, 1990-1991 (Box 77)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 77)
      - Students of Color of Rackham, 1991-1992 (Box 77)
      - Undergraduate Scholarship, 1994 (Box 77)
    - Recruitment
      - 1988-1989 (Box 77)
      - Trip, 11/13-11/16; 1990 (Box 77)
    - Regents
      - Fellowship, 1994 (Box 77)
      - Meeting, 2/15/1990 (Box 77)
    - Reorganization, 1989 (Box 77)
    - Representative Views about Cecil Miskel Leadership, 3/1992 (Box 77)
    - Retirement
      - 1990 (Box 77)
      - General, 1989 (Box 77)
    - Requests for Copyright Permission, 1989-1993 (Box 77)
    - Research Centers, 1988 (Box 77)
    - Robinson, Jay Meeting with, 12/1988 (Box 77)
    - Sharphorne, Daniel
      - 6/1/1994 (Box 77)
      - 6/5/1995 (Box 77)
    - Simpson and Kaufman, 11/17/1993 (Box 77)
    - Social Work, School of
      - Correspondence, 1989-1990; 1990-1991 (Box 77)
      - Divisional Library
        - 2/20/1989 (Box 77)
        - 3/22/1989 (Box 77)
        - Ad Hoc Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 77)
        - Program, 1990 (Box 78)
        - School of
          - General, 1990 (Box 78)
          - 1992-1993 (Box 78)
          - 1993-1994 (Box 78)
    - Software Education 794, 8/1/1994 (Box 78)
    - Special Education
      - Special Education Commission, 1980s-1990s; 5 folders (Box 78)
      - Working File--Special Education, 1990s (Box 78)
    - Society for College and University Planning (SCUP), 1991-1992 (Box 78)
    - Special Task Force for Statistical Support at the University of Michigan, 1989 (Box 78)
    - School of Education Strategic Planning Retreat, 1987 (Box 78)
    - Student Services, Office of
      - General, 1997 (Box 78)
      - Graduate Admission Reports, 1990 (Box 78)
    - Miscellaneous Surveys, 1997 (Box 78)
    - Tables
      - 1987-1988 (Box 78)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 78)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 78)
    - Taubman, A. Alfred